Update April 21, 2013:

New release Momods_Night_Scalper_V3.0

I'm pleased to release new version of my Night Scalper EA.

Main Features/Modifications:

- Auto-Timing (EA will determine your broker's GMT Offset automatically). No need to enter your GMT_offset. The EA will get time at New York from a webpage and compare it with your broker's server time to determine GMT Offset. This option is True by default. Thanks to maximo for providing the code. You still need to enter your GMT offset manually during back test. 

- Added Daylight Savings Time (DST). This option for back testing only. If your broker uses DST or you enabled DST when creating your FXT data file, please set this option to True during back test. No need to generate a new FXT file without DST to back test this EA. Please don't enable this option during live or demo trading.

- Added maximo's Fractal Level indicator. If you enable Show_Fractal_Levels, fractal levels will be displayed on your chart so you can watch entry levels. You need to download and add Fractal Levels indicator to your Indicators folder.

- Renamed some parameters to remove any confusion:
Trade_Spacing becomes Trade_Pause_On_Loss
Allow_Second_Trade becomes Allow_Second_Open_Trade


- Added another option for Trade Pause on Loss. Instead of pausing for a certain number of minutes, now you can pause trading based on price movement. To open another buy trade after loss, price must go lower for x pips. To open another Sell trade after loss, price must go higher by x pips. This is good option for those testing price charts ...renko.. range...) .

- Added RSI indicator as an extra filter in the Pro version. To open Buy trade, RSI must be higher than RSI_Entry and to open Sell trade, RSI must be lower than RSI_Entry.

Internal Settings for all pairs in the Basic Version are not changed. It is exactly the same as previous version. 

As in any new release, please use on demo account only. It might contain bugs.

Update April 2, 2013

New modified version Momods_Night_Scalper_v2.2

This release contains the two usual versions : Basic and Pro. 

- Fixed a bug in showing session status in the display.

Update March 31, 2013

"Momods_Night_Scalper_v2.1"

I'm pleased to release new version of my Night Scalper EA. As usual, we will have two versions: Basic and Pro. For more information about EA installation, pairs, TFs, ... etc, please refer to post #1 of this thread.

I spent the last few days coding and testing a new exit strategy based on decreasing profit with time. The aim was to decrease the number of trades that end with small loss and trying to exit with small profit or break-even instead. The results of my several tests were not encouraging at all. There were big difference in net profit compared to existing strategy. Using WPR and/or CCI for exit proved to be the best. Although you will have several small losses, but it will save you from many exits at full stop loss. Also, it allows you to follow trend for larger profit.

Main fixes/modifications:

- fixed the bug related to Thursday/Friday trading session.

- added Bollinger Bands as new signal/filter. BB can be used alone as primary entry signal or as a filter with other signals like WPR and CCI. I did not have enough time to test BB for different pairs. Therefore, the built-in settings in basic version don't use this filter yet.

- added trade pause after loss. If a trade ended in loss, the EA will not open a similar trade until x minutes has passed. This is to prevent multiple full SL as a result of sudden strong trend. This filter is set to false by default as if might reduce number of trades. It's up to the user to set it on/off.

- Modified built-in settings in Basic version for three pairs (EURCAD, EURGBP, and USDCAD). The modifications included increasing SL to 60 pips as it will improve both net profit and relative draw down (RDD).