Setup Procedure:

- Open 10 charts for the following pairs:
eurusd, eurgbp, eurcad, eurchf, gbpusd, gbpchf, gbpcad, usdcad, cadchf, and usdchf.
- change TF to M15 for all charts except EURUSD which should be M30.
- attach Momods_Night_Scalper_v3.0_Basic to each chart.
- make sure that DLL imports are allowed.
- the EA will automatically adjust to your broker's GMT offset.
- You are done and ready for trading.

For the Pro's, a Pro version is attached with all parameters in the externals. You need to put max spread for each pair, put your GMT offset, and for EURUSD you need to insert the attached set file.


Quick remarks:

- Second trade is disabled by default. If you enable this feature, you need to use proper money management. I recommend lowering risk to 5-7%. Enabling second trade might increase profit, but it will increase DD as well.

- I don't recommend trading any JPY, AUD, or NZD pair due to the opening of these markets. 

- I don't recommend trading outside default trading hours (20-23 GMT). You might get good results for a short while, but it's not good in the long term.

- Please don't use on your live account. There were lots of changes and there might be some bugs. Let's demo test it first.